xaxor.com 2012-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Xaxor

At xaXor.com (“the Website”) we take your privacy and the protection of your information seriously. Outlined below is our online Privacy Policy. By using the Website you are accepting our terms and practices under this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not continue to use the Website.

## Collection and disclosure of information

You are not required to provide information directly to us in order to view the site. There are no subscription forms for individuals to subscribe. Users can access and browse the site without disclosing any personal data.  
The type of information we collect includes ‘Personal Information’ and ‘Non-Personal Information’. Personal Information is the information you supply to us about yourself (name, e-mail, etc.) when you contact us using our [contact form](http://xaxor.com/contact) and/or [upload form](http://xaxor.com/submit) (for image submissions). Non-Personal Information incorporates web usage information collected by us as you use the Website such as browser type, your IP address, and user data to track usage of the Website. xaXor.com reviews standard web logs and uses Google Analytics that shows information such as what pages a visitor viewed on the web site, where they came from and how they left the site. This information is used for site quality improvement only.

## Our Use of Your Personal Information

We only use your information in order to respond to queries or requests submitted by you.

## Security of your Personal Information

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We will never share, lend, sell or disclose any personal information you decide to share with this Website.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, xaXor.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

xaXor.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on xaXor.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to xaXor.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on xaXor.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

xaXor.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. xaXor.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contact Information

You can contact us by e-mail at [Contact{at}xaxor.com](mailto:Contact@xaxor.com).
